<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<catalog journal="Oracle Magazine" publisher="Oracle Publishing">
	<article>
		<details> Magic-inspired everyone is by hearing this word, irrespective of how old or intelligent a person is. How does it feel to live magic and be a part of it? Not every magician is talented to make magic interactive and lively. This is what makes Stefan Ebinger, a corporate magician, entertainer and performer unique. He brings the three stages of magic- the pledge, the turn and the prestige to every eye staring at him. He takes you to his magical world and makes you feel enthralled by his performance. Gifted we are to experience such a surreal phenomenon come real in front of us at Kurukshetra'14 
</details>
<quotes>"Get Into The Magic World"</quotes>

<name>Boopathi Velu*Jayviz Selvin X</name>
<mobilenumber>91 7598284142*91 9487488163</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>A picture is worth a thousand words they say. What could be more impressive if the picture stands in front of us as though it’s real? Mr. Selva Kumar makes it true with his fascinating abilities in painting and digital editing. All he needs is some space and time to make you visualize anything you dream of. He can make pictures appear from the ground, which can be viewed by taking a photograph from a particular distance. There are no words to appreciate art and this piece of art makes an illusion seem almost real. All we can do is admire its beauty without the need of an explanation   
</details>
 <quotes>Space Trek Mobile Planetarium</quotes>
 
 <name>Hari Nattudurai*Hari Nattudurai</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9790490202 * 91 9790490202</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Disaster management is a vital part of a nation’s progress. Not everyone is aware of the special team working on it- the National Disaster response Force, NDRF in short. The kind of responsibilities undertaken by this body is breath taking. We at kurukshetra feel the necessity of sharing this knowledge with everyone and hence we have the team to briefly explain about the equipments used for relief during four major concerns namely ‘Medical First Responder’ , ‘Collapsed Structure and Search Relief’ and ‘Chemical Biological Radiological and Nuclear Emergency Relief’. It is now in our hands to know more of disaster management and be of help when in need. Here is an opportunity to give back !
</details>
<quotes>"DISASTER RELIEF EQUIPMENTS EXHIBITION"</quotes>
<name>N/A*N/A</name>
<mobilenumber> * </mobilenumber>

	</article>

	<article>
		<details>One would never forget their first ride on a motor cycle. For the stunt men out here, each ride is unforgettable. These men have overcome boundaries of fear, doubt and have achieved skills, skills which make our breath stop. Kurukshetra ’14 will take your breath away with these mind boggling stunts. Watch them hyper spin, switch back and perform wheelies. Do not give away this wonderful opportunity to boost your levels of adrenaline
</details>
<quotes>Apache Pro Show
</quotes>
<name>N/A*N/A</name>
<mobilenumber> * </mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>The field of sporting has been offering endless entertainment to mankind since its inception. What we learn out of sports is what makes it even more exclusive. The dedication, courage, perseverance, team work etc shown by the athletes have been lessons of life by themselves. Mr Sukumar here has immortalized their most prized moments by photographing them throughout the years. The pictures showcase emotions at their highest. Each one of them is a story on its own. It’s time to draw inspiration from them. 
</details>
<quotes>Sports Photo Exhibition</quotes>
<name>N/A*N/A</name>
<mobilenumber> * </mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>People who work in the metropolitan sewer system face a lot of problems like – Elephantitis, Poisoning, Hepatitis, skin infection, etc… Yeah!!! If not for these sacrificing people, our future plans of underground drainage system are total waste of money and effort. 
Also remember that these people aren’t born to do these works, and need to suffer from these disorders or diseases. We as engineers should enlighten them about the harmful effect of such harmful job at the earliest, that’s the simple part – telling advice to others… The hard part is – now who will clean up the drainage??? 
Answer for that is the “sewerbot “ – its water-proof, capable of clearing blocks, customized for Indian conditions, efficient and most importantly it doesn’t need a person to get into the manhole. Welcome, and look at our creation… 
</details>
<quotes>"Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn."
- Benjamin Franklin 
</quotes>
<name>Ashok Kumar*Ashok Kumar</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9095988597*91 9095988597</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>"Sustainability" has become the need of the hour. We have been exploiting energy all over the world for so long that now the awareness has crept in to make the best out of minimum resources at a minimal cost. Millions are spent in adopting advanced techniques to construct buildings in the western world. The time has come to make the world turn and look at India and its way of building in harmony with nature.Kurukshetra'14 is hosting "Build it like Baker" to show you that cost and luxury need not necessarily go hand in hand. Mr.Laurie Baker, famously known as “The Brick Master of Kerala”, was the pioneer of low cost nature-friendly housing in India. The session at K!14 will expose you to Laurie Baker’s architecture that aims at constructing at the minimum cost possible in the most eco-friendly manner, not only with lectures but also with a hands-on experience of building a real time structure in the campus of CEG. If cost effective eco building brings to your mind buildings with a somber finish, then this workshop will show you what reality is. So come and join us in our retrospective journey to explore the world of sustainable construction!
</details>
<quotes>"There's an old saying: manners maketh the man. I think they also make good architecture."

-	Laurie Baker</quotes>
<name>Ashok Kumar*Ashok Kumar</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9940028323*91 9489588922</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Concerts are where you can see trained musicians create magic with music from instruments. Kurukshetra 2014 is where you get to be a techno-musician and bring out digital music by just typing out lines of code! For the first time, put algorithms to use and create instantaneous music. Beyond music, live coding can also be used to generate dynamically changing visuals! You code and your output just flashes in the background. You can also make it move to your own music as you type on. Are you thinking twice because you have never touched any musical instrument in your life? Well you don’t have to for all you need is the patience to code and some creativity. If all these sound exciting then here is something that’s going to keep you glued to your laptop. Welcome to "LIVE CODING" workshop, the first of its kind in India, to saturate your creative quest. Code your way to musical euphoria!</details>
<quotes>"Limitations live only in our minds, but if we use our imaginations and creativity our possibilities become limitless."</quotes>
<name>Archana*Sri Ganesh</name>
<mobilenumber>91 7708038310*91 9789967312</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Are you fed up with the labyrinthine circuits? Do you despise the intricate embedded systems? Have you given up controlling all your controllers and processors? Do you want to look beyond the world of the paper and books? Well, here we are to take you from the academic level to the consumer world. Kurukshetra’14 provides you the perfect platform to transfigure the theories you have learnt all through your life into a great innovation. Get hold of an incredible opportunity to conquer the real-time control programming world using C2000 processors with the eminent guidance of an expert team from the most coveted "TEXAS INSTRUMENTS". We welcome you to participate and develop a motor control system using the 32 bit DSP engine.</details>
<quotes>"Scientists investigate that which already is; engineers create which has never been"</quotes>
<name>Yuvarani*Mystica</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9790999231*91 8903422492</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>In a time where undisturbed electricity has become a rarity, India is looking at all possible ways to generate electricity. And nuclear power, the fourth-largest source of electricity in India, has become indispensable indeed. In nuclear reactors, heat energy from nuclear fission is converted into electric energy. You say you already know it? Well, you might but get to know more about it because this much is not just enough! NuGen welcomes you into the world of Enrico Fermi and provides an opportunity to get first-hand knowledge of the what, when and how of a nuclear power plant. Register yourself and be one of the elite hundred to visit and explore the nuclear power plant at Kalpakkam! With Kurukshetra 2014, step into the realms of energy engineering! It is time to drop your books and start exploring the engineer in you.</details>
<quotes>"Nuclear power is here to stay, and we need to support a strong domestic uranium industry."
- Michael Burgess 
</quotes>
<name>Ranjith Kumar*Ilangoven  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9789253251*91 8754935089</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<details>Do you know how to write Objective C to make a native iOS app? What about Java to make Android apps? If you don't and all you know is HTML and CSS, worry not! You can still create mobile apps as Cross Platform MobApp is here to help you out! This workshop will help you take a quick look into the recent trends in mobile app development. Experts from IBM will be there to expose you to various tools in the industry such as Phonegap and IBM’s Worklight to build cross-platform mobile applications. There will also be a hands-on session where you get to experience building a mobile app. Register yourself for this workshop and do not miss this great opportunity, for only limited number of participants will be taken. </details>
<quotes>"We've arranged a civilization in which most crucial elements profoundly depend on science and technology."
- Carl Sagan</quotes>
<name>Praveen Prabhu*Kannan  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9047061174*91 8939735131</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<details>In a time where undisturbed electricity has become a rarity, India is looking at all possible ways to generate electricity. And nuclear power, the fourth-largest source of electricity in India, has become indispensable indeed. In nuclear reactors, heat energy from nuclear fission is converted into electric energy. You say you already know it? Well, you might but get to know more about it because this much is not just enough! NuGen welcomes you into the world of Enrico Fermi and provides an opportunity to get first-hand knowledge of the what, when and how of a nuclear power plant. Register yourself and be one of the elite hundred to visit and explore the nuclear power plant at Kalpakkam! With Kurukshetra 2014, step into the realms of energy engineering! It is time to drop your books and start exploring the engineer in you.

</details>
<quotes>"Education is not the learning of facts but the training of the mind to think"

-Albert Einstein</quotes>
<name>Ranjith Kumar*Ilangoven  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9789253251*91 8754935089</mobilenumber>
	</article>
</catalog>