<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<catalog journal="Oracle Magazine" publisher="Oracle Publishing">
	<article>
		<details>How many hours have you spent gazing at your mobile screen ever so intently in order to kill those pigs with your Angry birds? It is one of the most fun and addictive games in the modern day that we simply couldn’t get enough of! And yes, even we couldn’t get enough of it. So here at Kurukshetra 14, we present you a new version of Angry Birds- one that is bigger, better, more fun and more addictive and one that is played with bots. Come and play angry birds with us in a much bigger arena! After all, the fun is more when it gets bigger! 
</details>

<quotes>"The further you get into technology, the further you go into gaming. That's the general rule."
- Nick Johnson</quotes>
<name>Nihal*Iswarya</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9444742786*91 9176328510</mobilenumber>

	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Gone are the days when wars were fought with swords and axes. Today, we let our metal maniacs battle it out for us. War does not determine who is right but who is left. Kurukshetra presents to you Robowars! - A chance to test the mettle of your creation! It is time to get ready and prepare your bot for some of the greatest battles of all time, fought in a cage. Has your bot got the warrior in itself to defeat all counterparts and emerge victorious? At K!14, the fight is set to get bigger this time, with sophisticated arena weapons and many more surprises. This definitely means war! Let the preparations for the war begin. Watch this space for more updates about the war!</details>
<quotes>"War is young men dying and old men talking"

-  Troy</quotes>
<name>Afras*Ranjith</name>
<mobilenumber>91 8973255998*91 9566047167</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>"Cañon del Oro," guarded by the Apache spirits, is considered to be the land of hidden treasure.Many stories arising or deriving from the lost diggings have inspired many to search for lost Apache gold ever since.Its legend has supplied many folk tales, stories and books with ample fuel for fantasies of lost treasures, hidden canyons, Apache secrets and gold "somewhere out there" in the wilds. The villain, who comes to know about this hidden treasure, is furious over obtaining it. He captures our charming heroine and threatens the hero that in order to free his lady, he must look for that treasure and bring it to him. With advancements in technology and his skills in robotics, our hero plans to retrieve the treasure. But there are several hurdles that restrict the robot from entering the land of treasure.It then comes to light that several keys have to be found in order to open the gates of the land of treasure. There is also another gang that is determined to get the treasure before our hero does. But only one gets to fulfil his desire. Who will it be? Here is your chance to obtain the treasure of Apache with the latest technology and inventions in Kurukshetra 2014.Your task is to get the treasure before the other gang does.Before you start your quest for the treasure, you must make sure you’re ready and up for it.Pass the initial tests to reach the grand canyon of buried gold. Your clock is ticking!!! Tok tok tok!
</details>
<quotes>"It is the dim haze of mystery that adds enchantment to pursuit."
- Antoine Rivarol</quotes>
<name>Vigneshwaran*Murugesan</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9489238464*91 9486806119</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Do you think you are the most flamboyant robot designer in the whole world? Are you in constant search for challenges that could excite and motivate you to excel? Bored of robotic events with stereotyped problem statements? No limitations, no restrictions. Kurukshetra provides you the perfect opportunity to unleash your innovation and creativity. Designer's Quest is your chance to create an engineering marvel that will do more than just the task specified. So you think you can create?</details>
<quotes>"Creativity is thinking up new things. Innovation is doing new things."
— Theodore Levitt</quotes>
<name>Afrin*Rahul</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9677211955*91 9940118459</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>A small yellow creature travels through a maze collecting pellets while escaping from being eaten by its enemies. Sounds familiar? Pacman was a very simple yet highly addictive game that remained popular for a landmark 2 generations captivating kids and adults alike. As a tribute to this revolutionary game, Kurukshetra 2014 gives you an opportunity to relive the famous arcade game in a whole new dimension. PACBOT - A ROBOTIC Challenge like never before. PACBOT challenges you to capture the gold coins spread over the PAC MAZE combating against the Ghosts. An incredible chance to become the ultimate champion. Unleash The Power of Your PACBOT in Kurukshetra 2014!</details>
<quotes>"The further you get into technology, the further you go into gaming. That's the general rule."
- Nick Johnson</quotes>
<name>Afrin*Ranjith</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9677211955*91 9566047167</mobilenumber>

	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Who doesn't love an exhilarating day at a Grand Prix? That inevitable rush of adrenaline, the palpable excitement in the air and the spine-tingling suspense keeping you at the edge of your seat...!!! Experience all this and even more at GodSpeed - the event for racing fans. All you have to do is get your IC engine powered Radio Controlled buggy on the multi terrain track and set your racing spirit ablaze. If you are fast enough, the day and the grand prize could be yours!</details>
<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Nickelodeon Robot Wars is a game show that aired on Nickelodeon from August 25, 2002 to October 6, 2002. Hosted by Dave Aizer, the show was Nickelodeon's take on Robot Wars, the popular and long-running robot-fighting game show. The show was canceled after one season, and subsequently aired on Nickelodeon GAS.
The series of six shows was filmed at Shepperton Studios in England in January 2002 at the same time as the second season of the Robot Wars Extreme Warriors series shown on 'The New TNN' American television network (now Spike TV). Both shows featured American teams and robots flown to England for the filming.</details>
<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>It is a holy place and is also known as Dharmakshetra ("Holy Place"). According to the Puranas, Kurukshetra is named after King Kuru, the ancestor of Kauravas and Pandavas, as depicted in epic Mahabharata. The importance of the place is attributed to the fact that the Kurukshetra War of the Mahabharata was fought on this land and the Bhagavad Gita was preached on this land during the war when Lord Krishna found Arjuna in a terrible dilemma.</details>
		<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Nickelodeon Robot Wars is a game show that aired on Nickelodeon from August 25, 2002 to October 6, 2002. Hosted by Dave Aizer, the show was Nickelodeon's take on Robot Wars, the popular and long-running robot-fighting game show. The show was canceled after one season, and subsequently aired on Nickelodeon GAS.
The series of six shows was filmed at Shepperton Studios in England in January 2002 at the same time as the second season of the Robot Wars Extreme Warriors series shown on 'The New TNN' American television network (now Spike TV). Both shows featured American teams and robots flown to England for the filming.</details>
<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>It is a holy place and is also known as Dharmakshetra ("Holy Place"). According to the Puranas, Kurukshetra is named after King Kuru, the ancestor of Kauravas and Pandavas, as depicted in epic Mahabharata. The importance of the place is attributed to the fact that the Kurukshetra War of the Mahabharata was fought on this land and the Bhagavad Gita was preached on this land during the war when Lord Krishna found Arjuna in a terrible dilemma.</details>
		<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>
</catalog>