<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<catalog journal="Oracle Magazine" publisher="Oracle Publishing">
	<article>
		<details>RoS 2014 is the 8th edition of the online treasure hunt of Kurukshetra. Contained within this hunt, are a series of levels, along with clues, both visual and verbal and a plethora of labyrinths, mazes and puzzles that only the most intelligent and persistent of the competitors can survive. RoS fosters lateral thinking, on-the-spot multi tasking and probes into the deeper understanding of how the brain processes things and how best our train of thought works. RoS is widely popular and quite addicting due to its easy accessibility, universal understanding and fun trivia. The key to every riddle can be solved using your intellect and skill (luck will not lead you to the answer). Anyone anywhere in the world can uncover the clues and solve the riddles to discover the hidden treasure. So if you are an Indie Jones fan or have grown up yearning to be a treasure hunter like Miss Croft, fear not, RoS will bring you the same puzzling challenges and riddles at the comfort of your home. Stay tuned! Event starts at January 3rd, 2014 at 7.00 p.m. There will be a trial run on January 3rd 2014.
</details>
<quotes>"The true mystery of the world is the visible, not the invisible."

-	Oscar Wilde</quotes>
<name>Naveen S*Sainath R</name>
<mobilenumber>91 80156 86675*91 99405 69372</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>The charm of good puzzles is too tempting to avoid. Cerebra is the perfect recipie for those who yearn for the unique blend of mathematics combined with reasoning Cerebra is the ultimate online math puzzle challenge for the bunch of 'wanna be' mathematicians !!!
</details>
 <quotes>"The art of simplicity is a puzzle of complexity"
-   Douglas Horton</quotes>
<name>Mohit Bagde*Rajkiran Rajkumar</name>
<mobilenumber>91 98848 99154*91 95516 59212</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	

	<article>
		<details>What is Sherlock you ask? It is quite elementary, my dear participant. As the name clearly implies, the event is entirely about observation based on deduction, paying homage to the world's greatest detective. The second edition of the Detective RPG is bigger, more twisted, features a new character and continues the story in the same visual novel style as before. A stand alone mission by itself, with a few references to the previous edition, Sherlock promises to entertain and amaze like never before. Come participate in the 8th edition of Kurukshetra's online mystery event and match your wits against the greatest minds of the world in this Massively Multiplayer browser-based detective RPG.</details>
<quotes>"You are the master of your own destiny"</quotes>
<name>Jayanth*Kalyan</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9500199292*91 9677269859</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>There are no flamboyant explanations for Online Programming Contest. You are the master of your own destiny. You are supposed to make optimise your code, make it error free to tackle the time constraint and corner cases. Buckle up for one of the most brain draining contest in Kurukshetra 2014 !!!</details>
<quotes>"You are the master of your own destiny."
- William Somerset Maugham</quotes>
<name>Rajkiran Rajkumar*Jai Vasanth</name>
<mobilenumber>91 95516 59212*91 98652 76660</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	
	
	<article>
		<details>"Greed, for lack of a better word, is good". Gordon Gekko's cult dialogue sums up the very reason why anyone is doing anything in the Stock markets. Money makes the world go round and he who can invest well is the richer man. If you have it in you to take the 'Bull' by its horns and win or survive multiple 'Bear' hugs and lose and fall off, this game has been tailor-made for you. Be a part of India's biggest online mock stock market and rise to the top of this fictitious Wall Street. Dalal Bull provides a platform for stock market enthusiasts to show case their skill.</details>
<quotes>"Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it." - William Somerset Maugham
</quotes>
<name>Rajkiran Rajkumar*Jai Vasanth</name>
<mobilenumber>91 95516 59212*91 98652 76660</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<details>Greed, for lack of a better word, is good". Gordon Gekko's cult dialogue sums up the very reason why anyone is doing anything in the Stock markets. Money makes the world go round and he who can invest well is the richer man. If you have it in you to take the 'Bull' by its horns and win or survive multiple 'Bear' hugs and lose and fall off, this game has been tailor-made for you. Be a part of India's biggest online mock stock market and rise to the top of this fictitious Wall Street. Dalal Bull provides a platform for stock market enthusiasts to show case their skill.</details>
<quotes>Not Given</quotes>

	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Nickelodeon Robot Wars is a game show that aired on Nickelodeon from August 25, 2002 to October 6, 2002. Hosted by Dave Aizer, the show was Nickelodeon's take on Robot Wars, the popular and long-running robot-fighting game show. The show was canceled after one season, and subsequently aired on Nickelodeon GAS.
The series of six shows was filmed at Shepperton Studios in England in January 2002 at the same time as the second season of the Robot Wars Extreme Warriors series shown on 'The New TNN' American television network (now Spike TV). Both shows featured American teams and robots flown to England for the filming.</details>
<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>It is a holy place and is also known as Dharmakshetra ("Holy Place"). According to the Puranas, Kurukshetra is named after King Kuru, the ancestor of Kauravas and Pandavas, as depicted in epic Mahabharata. The importance of the place is attributed to the fact that the Kurukshetra War of the Mahabharata was fought on this land and the Bhagavad Gita was preached on this land during the war when Lord Krishna found Arjuna in a terrible dilemma.</details>
		<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Nickelodeon Robot Wars is a game show that aired on Nickelodeon from August 25, 2002 to October 6, 2002. Hosted by Dave Aizer, the show was Nickelodeon's take on Robot Wars, the popular and long-running robot-fighting game show. The show was canceled after one season, and subsequently aired on Nickelodeon GAS.
The series of six shows was filmed at Shepperton Studios in England in January 2002 at the same time as the second season of the Robot Wars Extreme Warriors series shown on 'The New TNN' American television network (now Spike TV). Both shows featured American teams and robots flown to England for the filming.</details>
<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>It is a holy place and is also known as Dharmakshetra ("Holy Place"). According to the Puranas, Kurukshetra is named after King Kuru, the ancestor of Kauravas and Pandavas, as depicted in epic Mahabharata. The importance of the place is attributed to the fact that the Kurukshetra War of the Mahabharata was fought on this land and the Bhagavad Gita was preached on this land during the war when Lord Krishna found Arjuna in a terrible dilemma.</details>
		<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>
</catalog>