<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<catalog journal="Oracle Magazine" publisher="Oracle Publishing">
	<article>
		<details>Have the interest of evading the State of the Art Security System? Have a great team? Do you know light well? Are you ready for the challenge? 
By this event, we assure you fun, excitement and teamwork. 
A project based event which will challenge the mind of budding engineers who are seeking day to day challenges. Basically this event concentrates on the principles of optics. Event challenges you both physically and mentally.
</details>
<quotes>"It is better to create than to learn! Creating is the essence of life"
-Julius Caesar</quotes>
<name>Guru*Guru</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9566139729*91 9566139729</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>You know how to sort the tiny resistors? 
Know the colour chart? 
Bored of sorting the resistors after completing the lab experiment? 

Well, we are giving you a break from that bore, routine, difficult task of sorting those small, tiny resistors… Throw all the used resistors into a box and forget it, this device guarantees you perfecting sorting and storing of resistors. This will save a lot of time and makes you leave a comment – “Job Well Done.”  
</details>
 <quotes>"By giving us the opinions of the uneducated, journalism keeps us in touch with the ignorance of the community."
- Oscar Wilde</quotes>
 <name>Nihal*Nihal</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9444742786*91 9444742786</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Want to know anything about a student? 
	Well you found the right place, in just few clicks you will get it. 
This is aportal for the students of CEG, which will have updates of all the events happening in and around the college. An authenticated database, where his/her achievements are verified and published making it easier for verification while applying for further studies or jobs. This makes it simpler for faculty personals for recommending a student for particular events or job or internships. 
This portal pools together students, faculties and clubs, thus making it a perfect platform for knowing each other.
</details>
<quotes>"Imagination is more important than knowledge." 
- Albert Einstein</quotes>
<name>Jaivasanth*Jaivasanth</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9865276660*91 9865276660</mobilenumber>

	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Let me put you in this situation – A warm sunny day, deserted highway road, a loud vrroommmm sound in the background… Guess what could it be? 

Yeah!!! You guessed it right; you’re in a car – dashing at 170km/h… Pretty fast right…… Hmmmm, imagine a car coming from nowhere and about to collide with your car…. 
At that speed, brakes fail, tires burst, car rotates, baaammmmm!!!! Accident!!! What do you do now??? Will you find a way to save yourself or will you search for your mobile phone to make a phone call? OMG!!! Obviously, my life, save it… 

We made that simpler, worry less, we developed a system which is capable of calling the 108 helpline for help… Does it sound lame? Yeah I know it does… Here is the fun part!!! 108 reach out to you via google maps… Wanna know how??? Come visit us!!!
</details>
<quotes>"Science can amuse and fascinate us all, but it is engineering that changes the world."
-Isaac Asimov</quotes>
<name>Noor Abdul*Noor Abdul</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9894486815*91 9894486815</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Have you avoided the tasty chilly, onion bujji and chutney just for the sake that they are not hygienic and visually appealing? 
You still understand, about what place am speaking about?? 
I am well indeed speaking about the best hangout places in chennai – Beaches. 
Understand this people, those huts are the ones that they can afford and make in those loose sands. We might ask ourselves, can we improves there status by giving a economically feasible solution for this. 
Obviously, yeah!!! We are engineers; we have solution for problems… A portable, economic, self-sustaining, hygienic shop that are designed and built exclusively for beach vendors. These huts are a facelift to the beaches, added to these functionality, they are very modular (i.e.) it is not designed for just one kind of vendors., it can be converted into anything ranging from a “shelter” to a “hut”. 
</details>
<quotes>"Come, Get you ideas funded.."</quotes>
<name>Sai Mohit *Sai Mohit </name>
<mobilenumber>91 8015832603*91 8015832603</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>People who work in the metropolitan sewer system face a lot of problems like – Elephantitis, Poisoning, Hepatitis, skin infection, etc… Yeah!!! If not for these sacrificing people, our future plans of underground drainage system are total waste of money and effort. 
Also remember that these people aren’t born to do these works, and need to suffer from these disorders or diseases. We as engineers should enlighten them about the harmful effect of such harmful job at the earliest, that’s the simple part – telling advice to others… The hard part is – now who will clean up the drainage??? 
Answer for that is the “sewerbot “ – its water-proof, capable of clearing blocks, customized for Indian conditions, efficient and most importantly it doesn’t need a person to get into the manhole. Welcome, and look at our creation… 
</details>
<quotes>"Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn."
- Benjamin Franklin 
</quotes>
<name>Ashok Kumar*Ashok Kumar</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9095988597*91 9095988597</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>"Sustainability" has become the need of the hour. We have been exploiting energy all over the world for so long that now the awareness has crept in to make the best out of minimum resources at a minimal cost. Millions are spent in adopting advanced techniques to construct buildings in the western world. The time has come to make the world turn and look at India and its way of building in harmony with nature.Kurukshetra'14 is hosting "Build it like Baker" to show you that cost and luxury need not necessarily go hand in hand. Mr.Laurie Baker, famously known as “The Brick Master of Kerala”, was the pioneer of low cost nature-friendly housing in India. The session at K!14 will expose you to Laurie Baker’s architecture that aims at constructing at the minimum cost possible in the most eco-friendly manner, not only with lectures but also with a hands-on experience of building a real time structure in the campus of CEG. If cost effective eco building brings to your mind buildings with a somber finish, then this workshop will show you what reality is. So come and join us in our retrospective journey to explore the world of sustainable construction!
</details>
<quotes>"There's an old saying: manners maketh the man. I think they also make good architecture."

-	Laurie Baker</quotes>
<name>Ashok Kumar*Ashok Kumar</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9940028323*91 9489588922</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Concerts are where you can see trained musicians create magic with music from instruments. Kurukshetra 2014 is where you get to be a techno-musician and bring out digital music by just typing out lines of code! For the first time, put algorithms to use and create instantaneous music. Beyond music, live coding can also be used to generate dynamically changing visuals! You code and your output just flashes in the background. You can also make it move to your own music as you type on. Are you thinking twice because you have never touched any musical instrument in your life? Well you don’t have to for all you need is the patience to code and some creativity. If all these sound exciting then here is something that’s going to keep you glued to your laptop. Welcome to "LIVE CODING" workshop, the first of its kind in India, to saturate your creative quest. Code your way to musical euphoria!</details>
<quotes>"Limitations live only in our minds, but if we use our imaginations and creativity our possibilities become limitless."</quotes>
<name>Archana*Sri Ganesh</name>
<mobilenumber>91 7708038310*91 9789967312</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Are you fed up with the labyrinthine circuits? Do you despise the intricate embedded systems? Have you given up controlling all your controllers and processors? Do you want to look beyond the world of the paper and books? Well, here we are to take you from the academic level to the consumer world. Kurukshetra’14 provides you the perfect platform to transfigure the theories you have learnt all through your life into a great innovation. Get hold of an incredible opportunity to conquer the real-time control programming world using C2000 processors with the eminent guidance of an expert team from the most coveted "TEXAS INSTRUMENTS". We welcome you to participate and develop a motor control system using the 32 bit DSP engine.</details>
<quotes>"Scientists investigate that which already is; engineers create which has never been"</quotes>
<name>Yuvarani*Mystica</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9790999231*91 8903422492</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>In a time where undisturbed electricity has become a rarity, India is looking at all possible ways to generate electricity. And nuclear power, the fourth-largest source of electricity in India, has become indispensable indeed. In nuclear reactors, heat energy from nuclear fission is converted into electric energy. You say you already know it? Well, you might but get to know more about it because this much is not just enough! NuGen welcomes you into the world of Enrico Fermi and provides an opportunity to get first-hand knowledge of the what, when and how of a nuclear power plant. Register yourself and be one of the elite hundred to visit and explore the nuclear power plant at Kalpakkam! With Kurukshetra 2014, step into the realms of energy engineering! It is time to drop your books and start exploring the engineer in you.</details>
<quotes>"Nuclear power is here to stay, and we need to support a strong domestic uranium industry."
- Michael Burgess 
</quotes>
<name>Ranjith Kumar*Ilangoven  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9789253251*91 8754935089</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<details>Do you know how to write Objective C to make a native iOS app? What about Java to make Android apps? If you don't and all you know is HTML and CSS, worry not! You can still create mobile apps as Cross Platform MobApp is here to help you out! This workshop will help you take a quick look into the recent trends in mobile app development. Experts from IBM will be there to expose you to various tools in the industry such as Phonegap and IBM’s Worklight to build cross-platform mobile applications. There will also be a hands-on session where you get to experience building a mobile app. Register yourself for this workshop and do not miss this great opportunity, for only limited number of participants will be taken. </details>
<quotes>"We've arranged a civilization in which most crucial elements profoundly depend on science and technology."
- Carl Sagan</quotes>
<name>Praveen Prabhu*Kannan  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9047061174*91 8939735131</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<details>In a time where undisturbed electricity has become a rarity, India is looking at all possible ways to generate electricity. And nuclear power, the fourth-largest source of electricity in India, has become indispensable indeed. In nuclear reactors, heat energy from nuclear fission is converted into electric energy. You say you already know it? Well, you might but get to know more about it because this much is not just enough! NuGen welcomes you into the world of Enrico Fermi and provides an opportunity to get first-hand knowledge of the what, when and how of a nuclear power plant. Register yourself and be one of the elite hundred to visit and explore the nuclear power plant at Kalpakkam! With Kurukshetra 2014, step into the realms of energy engineering! It is time to drop your books and start exploring the engineer in you.

</details>
<quotes>"Education is not the learning of facts but the training of the mind to think"

-Albert Einstein</quotes>
<name>Ranjith Kumar*Ilangoven  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9789253251*91 8754935089</mobilenumber>
	</article>
</catalog>