<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<catalog journal="Oracle Magazine" publisher="Oracle Publishing">
	<article>
		<details>RoS 2014 is the 8th edition of the online treasure hunt of Kurukshetra. Contained within this hunt, are a series of levels, along with clues, both visual and verbal and a plethora of labyrinths, mazes and puzzles that only the most intelligent and persistent of the competitors can survive. RoS fosters lateral thinking, on-the-spot multi tasking and probes into the deeper understanding of how the brain processes things and how best our train of thought works. RoS is widely popular and quite addicting due to its easy accessibility, universal understanding and fun trivia. The key to every riddle can be solved using your intellect and skill (luck will not lead you to the answer). Anyone anywhere in the world can uncover the clues and solve the riddles to discover the hidden treasure. So if you are an Indie Jones fan or have grown up yearning to be a treasure hunter like Miss Croft, fear not, RoS will bring you the same puzzling challenges and riddles at the comfort of your home.Stay tuned! MAIN EVENT starts on January 5th, 2014 at 7.00 p.m.
</details>
<quotes>Main Run has begun. To play the game. Go to Link: http://kurukshetra.org.in/ros/</quotes>
<name>Naveen S.Sainath R</name>
<mobilenumber>91 80156 86675.91 99405 69372</mobilenumber>

	</article>

	<article>
		<details>A Day at the Races!!! Rev up your engines!!! Need for speed is absolutely most wanted to cross the gates of this crucible event.Xompeting with the crackerjacks of the world in racing is the toughest part. With these thrills in the dusty floor, with the sound of the roaring engines and the enliven spectators with blood surging veins it’s all set to bang the stupendous K! 2014. Get ready for the near-death experience at GOD SPEED!!!</details>
 <quotes>"The racing driver's mind has to have the ability to have amazing anticipation, coordination, and reflex. Because of the speed the car goes.

-Emerson Fittipaldi"</quotes>
 <name>Pradeep N S.Prasath R</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9842736668.91 9788069346</mobilenumber>
 
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>What do modern mathematicians actually do? What problems are of interest today? Do you think you can handle this king of all sciences in a better way than others? Then you have landed in the right place! It is that time of the year again, when battles are fought on the head, ideas and model triumph over one another! Math Modelling at Kurukshetra’14 offers you a prime platform to unleash your mathematical skills! Compete with some of the best logical minds across the country to arrive at the most suitable model for complex phenomena! 
 </details>
 <quotes>"Numbers constitute the only universal language." - Nathaneal West</quotes>
 <name>Narain Sharma.Hemalatha</name>
<mobilenumber>91 74011 58859.91 99624 59596</mobilenumber>
 
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Sketching, painting and printing have been the conventional ways of visualizing one’s perceptions. But at Kurukshetra, dare to dream beyond all these – Dare to create! Creation is the most complex magic in real life. Watch it come alive before your eyes at K! 14. Experience being the creator by creating 3D objects of virtually any shape from just digital models. A chance to create your own world as you learn the basics of 3D printing. Kurukshetra 2014 presents the 3D printing workshop, which will help you transform your visualization into reality - quite literally.Each participant will walk away with a wide understanding of 3D printing technology, related tools and materials and a greater sense of how this technology can be used commercially. By the end of the day every participant will have a takeaway 3D printed model created all by themselves. 3D printing is the latest thing in town and make sure you are a pioneer of this new technology! Registration Started !!!!</details>
<quotes> "It is better to create than to learn! Creating is the essence of life"
	
-Julius Caesar</quotes>
 <name>Vasupradha.Hussain</name>
<mobilenumber>91 7598272146.91 8056138027</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Every human is born intelligent but it is the creativity of the mind that decides your level of intellectual supremacy. Intelligence is being able to integrate human ideas with available materials and bringing them to reality by creating a model. But innovation lies in giving life to materials which are branded as "scrap". INNOVATE is where your spirit for innovation will face the ultimate challenge of building models from scrap materials.</details>
<quotes>"Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower"

    -  Steve Jobs</quotes>
 <name>Kishore Kumar.Anjana</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9094958912.91 9840454378</mobilenumber>

	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Greed, for lack of a better word, is good". Gordon Gekko's cult dialogue sums up the very reason why anyone is doing anything in the Stock markets. Money makes the world go round and he who can invest well is the richer man. If you have it in you to take the 'Bull' by its horns and win or survive multiple 'Bear' hugs and lose and fall off, this game has been tailor-made for you. Be a part of India's biggest online mock stock market and rise to the top of this fictitious Wall Street. Dalal Bull provides a platform for stock market enthusiasts to show case their skill.</details>
<quotes>Dalal Bull main event has now started, Check With Website.</quotes>
 <name>Rajkiran Rajkumar.Jai Vasanth</name>
<mobilenumber>91 95516 59212.91 98652 76660</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Nickelodeon Robot Wars is a game show that aired on Nickelodeon from August 25, 2002 to October 6, 2002. Hosted by Dave Aizer, the show was Nickelodeon's take on Robot Wars, the popular and long-running robot-fighting game show. The show was canceled after one season, and subsequently aired on Nickelodeon GAS.
The series of six shows was filmed at Shepperton Studios in England in January 2002 at the same time as the second season of the Robot Wars Extreme Warriors series shown on 'The New TNN' American television network (now Spike TV). Both shows featured American teams and robots flown to England for the filming.</details>
<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>It is a holy place and is also known as Dharmakshetra ("Holy Place"). According to the Puranas, Kurukshetra is named after King Kuru, the ancestor of Kauravas and Pandavas, as depicted in epic Mahabharata. The importance of the place is attributed to the fact that the Kurukshetra War of the Mahabharata was fought on this land and the Bhagavad Gita was preached on this land during the war when Lord Krishna found Arjuna in a terrible dilemma.</details>
		<quotes>Mandatory</quotes>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Nickelodeon Robot Wars is a game show that aired on Nickelodeon from August 25, 2002 to October 6, 2002. Hosted by Dave Aizer, the show was Nickelodeon's take on Robot Wars, the popular and long-running robot-fighting game show. The show was canceled after one season, and subsequently aired on Nickelodeon GAS.
The series of six shows was filmed at Shepperton Studios in England in January 2002 at the same time as the second season of the Robot Wars Extreme Warriors series shown on 'The New TNN' American television network (now Spike TV). Both shows featured American teams and robots flown to England for the filming.</details>
<quotes>Mandatory
     
 </quotes>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>It is a holy place and is also known as Dharmakshetra ("Holy Place"). According to the Puranas, Kurukshetra is named after King Kuru, the ancestor of Kauravas and Pandavas, as depicted in epic Mahabharata. The importance of the place is attributed to the fact that the Kurukshetra War of the Mahabharata was fought on this land and the Bhagavad Gita was preached on this land during the war when Lord Krishna found Arjuna in a terrible dilemma.</details>
		<quotes>Mandatory
     
 </quotes>
	</article>
</catalog>