<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<catalog journal="Oracle Magazine" publisher="Oracle Publishing">
	<article>
		<details>Sketching, painting and printing have been the conventional ways of visualizing one’s perceptions. But at Kurukshetra, dare to dream beyond all these – Dare to create! Creation is the most complex magic in real life. Watch it come alive before your eyes at K14! Experience being the creator by creating 3D objects of virtually any shape from just digital models. Here is your chance to create your own world as you learn the basics of 3D printing. Kurukshetra 2014 presents the 3D printing workshop, which will help you transform your visualization into reality - quite literally. Each participant will walk away with a broad spectrum understanding of 3D printing technology, related tools and materials and a greater sense of how this technology can be used commercially. By the end of the day every participant will have a takeaway 3D printed model created all by themselves. 3D printing is the latest thing in town and make sure you are a pioneer of this new technology!</details>
<quotes>"It is better to create than to learn! Creating is the essence of life"
-Julius Caesar</quotes>
<name>Vasupradha*Hussain</name>
<mobilenumber>91 7598272146*91 8056138027</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>In a world filled with sound bites and paparazzi-snapped photos, there are still storytellers determined to create media with meaning. From citizen journalism to feature films , their work is worth spreading. Have you ever wondered what it is to be in their shoes and experience this paparazzi first hand? Then this is your chance! Join the journalism workshop and get a chance to interact with eminent journalists and media personalities.
 </details>
 <quotes>"By giving us the opinions of the uneducated, journalism keeps us in touch with the ignorance of the community."
- Oscar Wilde</quotes>
 <name>Vinothini*KaviyaPriya</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9003673761*91 8883198877</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>When curiosity, creativity and a vision combine, innovations are born in this world. One such innovation was the robot. The thought of having a mechanical device mimic few human actions excited the entire human race. What’s more! They are not anymore emotionally invalid, for “Robots controlled by Facial Expressions” has become a reality! At Robotics Workshop of K! 14, get to know more about these bots incorporated with gesture sensing and processing techniques that can detect and mimic human facial expressions. We are here with an expert team to give you a hands-on experience of this remarkable technology. You need not be an expert in robotics; your passion for science is more than enough!</details>
<quotes>"Imagination is more important than knowledge." 
- Albert Einstein</quotes>
<name>Sundararaman*Harish</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9094850265*91 9940537951</mobilenumber>

	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Science and technology have immense potential; many of which still remains untapped. Come to Kurukshetra 14, the biggest battle of brains where we push the boundaries of science and realize new possibilities.Over the past decade, mobile phones have made communication easier for the common man. But ever thought of using them to control a robot? Imagine your chores getting done by just a single touch on your mobile. Live your imagination with the BLUETOOTH ROBOT at the K!14 Robotics workshop.With mobile phones becoming a necessity in today's world, let's tap their unexplored potential and make uncertain possibilities a reality. It's time to give new meaning to science.</details>
<quotes>"Science can amuse and fascinate us all, but it is engineering that changes the world."
-Isaac Asimov</quotes>
<name>Lakshmi Narayanan*Kumarappan</name>
<mobilenumber>91 8056435407*91 8056138027</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Welcome! This introduction is addressed to all those who are at the crossroads of choosing an alternative career. The life of an entrepreneur.But there are those few thoughts of unpreparedness that are holding you back ,though you have a great idea of your own.You also have a strong feeling that you will even make money through the idea. So, let's assume now that you are starting up. Then you will certainly have the problem of scaling,how do you scale? Added to that you would certainly wonder how will you handle millions of customers? How will you generate funds?And the biggest of all how to do all these things in a short span of time? These constitute few of the essential aspects you need to figure out in your start up. Join us with your brilliant idea and Learn about great businesses that have scaled, sometimes using a Venture Capitalist and some times even without them. Along with Learning how this market works in our country, at the scaling and Venture Capitalist workshop.</details>
<quotes>"Come, Get you ideas funded.."</quotes>
<name>Vivek*Shashank</name>
<mobilenumber>91 7401647058*91 9940129395</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Being a pioneer is not new to Kurukshetra for it has always been in the frontline when it comes to undertaking any first-of-its-kind initiative. One such is Krithi, a workshop exclusively for school students of standards 9,10 and 11. Kurukshetra workshops cater to enthusiastic minds of every age group and true to that, Krithi has been triumphant in giving students from schools across the country, a taste of engineering with innovative themes like Trebuchet modelling, Ornithopter Designing and Automata Building in its previous editions. This year get ready to delve into the world of Hydraulic cranes! Ever wondered how an apparently slim beam could withstand tonnes of weight? Ever wanted to explore its working principle? But, do you ask what is new, when you study all this in your textbooks? Well, the experience is indeed going to be new, for Krithi is offering you an opportunity to build your own miniature of a hydraulic crane!</details>
<quotes>"Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn."
- Benjamin Franklin 
</quotes>
<name>Harishankar*Iswarya</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9715442929*91 8012824509</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>"Sustainability" has become the need of the hour. We have been exploiting energy all over the world for so long that now the awareness has crept in to make the best out of minimum resources at a minimal cost. Millions are spent in adopting advanced techniques to construct buildings in the western world. The time has come to make the world turn and look at India and its way of building in harmony with nature.Kurukshetra'14 is hosting "Build it like Baker" to show you that cost and luxury need not necessarily go hand in hand. Mr.Laurie Baker, famously known as “The Brick Master of Kerala”, was the pioneer of low cost nature-friendly housing in India. The session at K!14 will expose you to Laurie Baker’s architecture that aims at constructing at the minimum cost possible in the most eco-friendly manner, not only with lectures but also with a hands-on experience of building a real time structure in the campus of CEG. If cost effective eco building brings to your mind buildings with a somber finish, then this workshop will show you what reality is. So come and join us in our retrospective journey to explore the world of sustainable construction!
</details>
<quotes>"There's an old saying: manners maketh the man. I think they also make good architecture."

-	Laurie Baker</quotes>
<name>Sai Pranay*Sriniwas</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9940028323*91 9489588922</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>Concerts are where you can see trained musicians create magic with music from instruments. Kurukshetra 2014 is where you get to be a techno-musician and bring out digital music by just typing out lines of code! For the first time, put algorithms to use and create instantaneous music. Beyond music, live coding can also be used to generate dynamically changing visuals! You code and your output just flashes in the background. You can also make it move to your own music as you type on. Are you thinking twice because you have never touched any musical instrument in your life? Well you don’t have to for all you need is the patience to code and some creativity. If all these sound exciting then here is something that’s going to keep you glued to your laptop. Welcome to "LIVE CODING" workshop, the first of its kind in India, to saturate your creative quest. Code your way to musical euphoria!</details>
<quotes>"Limitations live only in our minds, but if we use our imaginations and creativity our possibilities become limitless."</quotes>
<name>Archana*Sri Ganesh</name>
<mobilenumber>91 7708038310*91 9789967312</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	<article>
		<details>Are you fed up with the labyrinthine circuits? Do you despise the intricate embedded systems? Have you given up controlling all your controllers and processors? Do you want to look beyond the world of the paper and books? Well, here we are to take you from the academic level to the consumer world. Kurukshetra’14 provides you the perfect platform to transfigure the theories you have learnt all through your life into a great innovation. Get hold of an incredible opportunity to conquer the real-time control programming world using C2000 processors with the eminent guidance of an expert team from the most coveted "TEXAS INSTRUMENTS". We welcome you to participate and develop a motor control system using the 32 bit DSP engine.</details>
<quotes>"Scientists investigate that which already is; engineers create which has never been"</quotes>
<name>Yuvarani*Mystica</name>
<mobilenumber>91 9790999231*91 8903422492</mobilenumber>
	</article>

	<article>
		<details>In a time where undisturbed electricity has become a rarity, India is looking at all possible ways to generate electricity. And nuclear power, the fourth-largest source of electricity in India, has become indispensable indeed. In nuclear reactors, heat energy from nuclear fission is converted into electric energy. You say you already know it? Well, you might but get to know more about it because this much is not just enough! NuGen welcomes you into the world of Enrico Fermi and provides an opportunity to get first-hand knowledge of the what, when and how of a nuclear power plant. Register yourself and be one of the elite hundred to visit and explore the nuclear power plant at Kalpakkam! With Kurukshetra 2014, step into the realms of energy engineering! It is time to drop your books and start exploring the engineer in you.</details>
<quotes>"Nuclear power is here to stay, and we need to support a strong domestic uranium industry."
- Michael Burgess 
</quotes>
<name>Ranjith Kumar*Ilangoven  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9789253251*91 8754935089</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<details>Do you know how to write Objective C to make a native iOS app? What about Java to make Android apps? If you don't and all you know is HTML and CSS, worry not! You can still create mobile apps as Cross Platform MobApp is here to help you out! This workshop will help you take a quick look into the recent trends in mobile app development. Experts from IBM will be there to expose you to various tools in the industry such as Phonegap and IBM’s Worklight to build cross-platform mobile applications. There will also be a hands-on session where you get to experience building a mobile app. Register yourself for this workshop and do not miss this great opportunity, for only limited number of participants will be taken. </details>
<quotes>"We've arranged a civilization in which most crucial elements profoundly depend on science and technology."
- Carl Sagan</quotes>
<name>Praveen Prabhu*Kannan  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9047061174*91 8939735131</mobilenumber>
	</article>
	
	<article>
		<details>In a time where undisturbed electricity has become a rarity, India is looking at all possible ways to generate electricity. And nuclear power, the fourth-largest source of electricity in India, has become indispensable indeed. In nuclear reactors, heat energy from nuclear fission is converted into electric energy. You say you already know it? Well, you might but get to know more about it because this much is not just enough! NuGen welcomes you into the world of Enrico Fermi and provides an opportunity to get first-hand knowledge of the what, when and how of a nuclear power plant. Register yourself and be one of the elite hundred to visit and explore the nuclear power plant at Kalpakkam! With Kurukshetra 2014, step into the realms of energy engineering! It is time to drop your books and start exploring the engineer in you.

</details>
<quotes>"Education is not the learning of facts but the training of the mind to think"

-Albert Einstein</quotes>
<name>Ranjith Kumar*Ilangoven  </name>
<mobilenumber>91 9789253251*91 8754935089</mobilenumber>
	</article>
</catalog>